Voices collide, the storm and the flame. Laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive. In Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
are dancing torchlight in hand let's start the show
hi some guys hey Hansey how are you it was good time well I don't know you know
who I met you know who I saw on Instagram today is Danny Ranger I love
Not Danny ranger. I thought him to a danger ranger
new danger ranger is
He's uh
He's a streamer. I think he I don't know if he's on it. I beat you. I don't think he did
He might be but uh
He's like see like south and he said he might stop by I'm soon to the show. He's really cool
How are we doing like do you like this?
You like that? Yeah, I do have, you know, I've been really, like, looking into, like,
decoding myself, and you can decode yourself by, like, looking into numerology and looking
at, you know, your name and the numerology of your name, and then, you know, learning
Well, because, and I really hope not, I did see like there's something about the dog
and that they took the dog to the vet, I mean, it's like, I don't know, you might have to
tell me privately about that, but, okay, well, certainly don't support that, but I don't
What's up easy sorry to have a avenue song
He's horrific, uh-oh
well
Maybe never discuss you with them and see what's up. I don't know. I'm gonna
Okay, ready for a song here
Supercorn's child with a master plan
Building kingdoms from dust and bone
Shaping the world with will alone
Every shadow bends before the flame
Every trial calls your name
Waste of the cosmos, crystal clear
Lightfarer, torch in the storm
Born of the mountain, breaking the norm
Aquarius moon, the seer of skies
Vision of freedom, in ancient ice
Where the arrows shine
Secret temples of love untold
never decays
the gracious one, the best and seer
leader, teacher, forever here
oh my god
you know what, sometimes it's good to have a discussion with those people
Maybe we can check and maybe ask him if he comes but I probably won't talk but you know
Yeah, I like this guy
be cool like you could like probably like finally pretty quick but it's okay
human like the song
I should not pick them up
okay so
I'm going to leave this
For just starting out to sell because you know, I just don't want you guys
What's up, hey, what's up, bro? What's up? How are you? I'm good, man. I'm just fucking you know, I got a story
Me turn light on here
Listen, bro fucking up. I'm getting drunk dude. Who else is getting drunk?
What's up
Hey you got your head shaved? What did you do to your hair? Hold on.
What are you talking about?
Are you bald? What's going on? Did you have hair?
Yeah, I'm a skinhead. I'm a fucking peckerwood, dude.
What are you talking about? Fuck it. I eat dog all day.
San Bernardino peckerwoods.
Okay. I dated a peckerwood when I was in LA County Jail.
I know. You told me about it. I know. Hey, here's the guy.
It's like, I love you, dog.
Hey, man. Listen, I'm being serious right now, dog. Like, fuck it. I have to move.
Out of here where I live right now fucking hey, I might come through can I chill?
Yeah
Where you were doing like a Santa Monica or a sense?
On a beach on a beach we don't like fucking here's thing bro fucking. Yeah, I'll come through dude type shit
You know I mean like fucking uh
Yeah, you're cool, dude like you know fuck. Hey, you think I fucking uh
No, I'm not gonna say it online on the internet, you know, okay? Okay. Okay. We'll talk privately, okay? Yeah, but like your thing like
Yeah, like I'll hit you up like you have an Instagram or something like fucking don't leak your shit don't leak your shit, but I
Fuck it. I'll come through it. Listen. I'll have money. I'll have hella money
I have like fucking a hundred thousand dollars doc when I would have to leave this house
I'll have a hundred thousand dollars in my bank come on type shit, but you know me so
Come on through. I got you
Yeah, we'll fuck it. Hey, we'll listen hey money talks broke you guys want to see me and psych fucking on chatter bait
How much
How much? You know what I mean? Like I'm down. I'm you know, I mean type shit
So anyway, nice. Okay. Here. Here's the kitty cat
Hell yeah
Yeah, I was like, you know, I mean I was like have my hat. I was on my hat
Yeah, obviously you don't know me very well. You're like thinking that I support what you've been saying. Hold on a second.
I don't know. You just don't get me. You don't get me.
Now there's he.
But I have a song for you.
I shouldn't have thought out
A part of my brain was fried
I thought that I could win
But the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me?
They said I wasn't reasonable
Nothing was debatable with me
I tried to flood and pull
And over all the mods who fed me
But what they didn't see
Is that I am still me
It suits you.
Hi, guys.
That song is based on a Lisa Jordanna song.
Chris K, I think you're a little bit, I don't know if I can trust you, you know, I don't
know if I can trust you, so as fun as it would be to be on Chatterbait with you, and respectfully
Yeah, well, that's why I'd like to have controversial people on and we can check and discuss it with them, right?
So
It's a part of like part of what I do is like
Like letting people be themselves and so it's like I like to see first meeting the real first the real self, right?
Well, not if they're hurting an animal, but of course like I would like to
By all of what it's by by me being like a revealer I revealed to the Chris K stuff
Are you in place?
Yeah, you got punched in the face by the door. Oh
My god the dog that he has it's terrible
Okay, well
My logos but he looks kind of like he's suffered from a male pattern baldness a little bit
I like it. I'm gonna change it actually made a few
So how are you guys doing today? And hopefully it's a nice day. It's like
Well, it's already night time isn't it? Oh, it's the three four five
Kind of seen anybody on really
Since I woke up. Oh, yeah, this is pretty cool. I don't know if you saw this one
Who did there we go
Who called you that? George Wallace? Oh, no, but I think George Wallace is a troll, isn't he?
I don't think he's had anything nice to say to me ever.
So, you know, I wouldn't be too...
It's like that's like the number one thing that they like to call people.
Just like now...
I mean, I've heard everybody be called that.
Yeah, that's an anime.
I hope I would look like that, right?
It looks like me, you know, I'm gonna fix my camera.
Got the full screen.
Ah, there we go.
That's pretty cool, I got the tarot cards there too, yay.
Yeah, George Wallace, I don't know, I think him and
See part of the that gang that's pressing
So oh my gosh, I have to in order to get another camera. That'd be so cool. Oh my god, so expensive
You know how much the next up
Streamer thing is I said I would get 4k right maybe 4k video that'd be pretty cool
multi-stream to eight destinations. That'd be pretty cool. I could do all, like, I
could just always stream to all those places. I get an extra camera, 15 backstage
participants, four hours of pre-recorded streams, on-air webinars, a thousand
Like team seats better. I don't need the seats. I don't I like I don't like doing that anymore
But okay, but the one I get has full HD has no logo. I can stream to three destinations
I get the logos overlays video clips and the backgrounds to use I can have 10 on-screen participants
I can have two hours of pre-recorded streams unlimited streaming and recording
My live streams are recorded. Unlimited local recordings. Custom RTMP destinations.
That means I can stream on Rumble and stuff. Guest destinations, they can stream to their thing.
50 hours of permanent storage, intro and outro video.
It does AI clips for me, a custom referral message, 16 custom layouts, chat overlay and
that's a lot of good stuff, that's a lot of like, well I still might ask you because
I'd like to like question one about that but I know it sounds terrible, I still think
Yeah, I would like to use the extra camera
But because I'd be cool for like
Tarot readings and stuff, but I
suppose I can still get I can still get away with one but
Rg it's like what you go to controversial people like why am I like not allowed to have people pieces
It's one can interview Charles Bansen
I can I can interview somebody and it's maybe like I can be a good influence on them or like some kind of like
Maybe chat. We'll ask a question or something. It's like why why like not want to hear from the person again. Yeah, I
Don't want to I don't yeah, well, I can't watch. I mean it's like
It's like watching that would be too difficult for me. I can't watch stuff
Man, I don't like the idea of it. I have a good question about it
Thank you. Thank you. I will I'll do my show. I'll do it. It's like, you know, it's like some people will like me
Some people won't it's like gone to the point now or it's like
You know, I'm just gonna be myself because people like like me or not like, you know, it's like
Many people that they love me that's that hate me so might as well
Just do what I want. I'm not gonna please
probably either side
Completely, but maybe I can
Make both sides mostly happy
Well, I don't want to be the haters happy, but you know what I mean
Okay, I know you don't like sass and I don't like yeah
Content, please cooking content. Who's the content? Oh, yeah, so yeah, I know a content music
I have another song though
This one is called okay, so this is called okay, so this is about like, you know
I researched like on my birthday what like, you know angels and demons would like correspond to my birthday, right?
They got and basically then I can see what they're they're about and also it's like they're probably
Related some way to my birthday. So and there's a connection already there, right?
So I'll show you this
Okay, let's see.
Sorry, I'm taking forever, okay.
So these are like
these three, whatever I did, I put it into a song, right?
desktop document. Okay, there's docs. Okay, I made these little, these cool, like, prayer cards for them too.
Okay, one, two, three. Okay.
Okay, but I do believe in like, you know, also like working with like
Both your angel and your demon, right? I think I like not playing both sides, but I don't think I think it's more like
Being in touch with both sides, okay, and and also I think a lot of the demons were like just basically demonized, but
That's a story as a controversial topic
or if I need to fix that, I should come on.
That's the wrong bus stop.
I have two angels too, and that's the, um, death top, John.
Okay, I think I found it, got it.
Okay, let's see how this turned out.
So enjoy your day.
No, I'll be back.
Okay
See how this turns out.
I'll go to the chat while we do this.
Well, I'll be during the slideshow too.
Thank you for your patience guys.
When shadows rise, voices slander
When errors weigh upon my name
It's real, the healer answers
Turns my faults to sacred
With skills of truth and scrawl of learning
He binds the cracks that pain had torn
Through his hands, my soul returning
Every scar, a crown, reborn
Three who walk beside
the sea
The cosmos can see
I've been missing in my sleep
I'm trying to say